I sell dating services to single men.
Revenue, we range between 250 to 900.
I consistently live stream.
That's how I do everything.
Nothing has really changed in what I do,
but I'm seeing all metrics shrink
and it's like, I'm freaking out.
Yeah, no, I hear you.
At the simplest level, one of two things changed.
Either you change something unknowingly,
which is the concept's not as good
or it's not as compelling or whatever,
or something else changed,
which is either the environment changed,
so maybe it sounds tone deaf now,
or the algorithm changed
in terms of how it's pushing out lives.
There's a group of people I'm associated with
and they've all kind of been throttled as well.
They used to do like three, 400,
now they're on like one-ish.
That doesn't sound like shadow panning.
Okay.
Going from like 300 to 100 just sounds like
YouTube has shifted over time
and we just need to adapt to what's working now.
We've had to change our stuff all the time.
I think it's just like, you learn a trick, it worked,
it was a great ride, and now you have to change again.